Santa's in town early this year.
The Christmas Chronicles is a comedy, adventure,
family film directed by Clay Kaytis.
Siblings Kate and Teddy try to prove Santa Claus is real, but when they
accidentally cause his sleigh to crash, they have to save Christmas.
Kate Pierce, played by Darby Camp.
Teddy Pierce, played by Judah Lewis.
Santa Claus, played by Kurt Russell.
Dave Poveda, played by Martin Roach.
Mikey Jameson, played by Lamorne Morris.
Claire Pierce, played by Kimberly Williams-Paisley.
The Christmas Chronicles is a 2018 American Christmas comedy film
directed by Clay Kaytis from a screenplay by Matt Lieberman.
The film stars Kurt Russell, Judah Lewis, Darby Camp, Lamorne
Morris, Kimberly Williams-Paisley, and Oliver Hudson.
It is the first installment in The Christmas Chronicles film series.
The film was produced by 1492 Pictures and Wonder Worldwide and
was released on November 22, 2018, on Netflix.
The plot follows two children, Kate and Teddy, who notice Santa Claus in their home and jump into his sleigh with
his reindeer; however, they accidentally cause the sleigh to crash, and the presents are lost.
As Christmas morning approaches, it is up to the children and Santa to
save Christmas by correctly delivering all of the presents.
The Christmas Chronicles received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel, titled The Christmas Chronicles 2, was released on November
25, 2020, with much of the original cast returning.
The film explores themes of holiday, brother,
camera, santa claus, massachusetts.
The tone is lighthearted.